Contact

aubrosepescadero@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/aubrainvirtual (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

HTML

WordPress

Technical Support

Languages

Japanese (Elementary)

Certifications

Technical Support Fundamentals Introduction to HTML5

Interactivity with JavaScript

Electrical Installation and Maintenance NCII

Advanced Styling with Responsive Design

Publications

De-husked Coconut Quality Evaluation using Image Processing and Machine Learning Techniques

Aubrey Rose Pescadero

Computer Engineer | IT/CRM Officer at Dev Partners Recruitment Metro Davao

Summary

Strong information technology professional with over 2 years of experience working as an IT and with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Engineering from the University of Mindanao. Currently connected in IT Recruitment Industry as a Client Relations Officer and IT Officer.

Experienced Information Technology Support with a demonstrated history of working in BPO and the consumer goods industry. Skilled in Structured Cabling, Computer Networks, Installation and Configuration of Computer Systems and Server Administration, Hardware and Software Maintenance, and Troubleshooting.

Seminars/Webinars/Training Attended:

- -DICT MC3: Foundations on CERT Operations (2021)
- -DICT MC3: Training on Cybersecurity Competency Framework(2021)
- -DICT LC3: Python Programming Essentials Training (2021)
- -DICT Digital Jobs PH Training Wordress Web Development (2020)
- -Online Skills Training of Project CAWAN-AI Data Labeling Tool (2020)
- -Lego Educational Robotics and Computer Technical Training (2018)
- -OHS Orientation for SafeYouth@Work (2018, DOLE)

Experience

Dev Partners Recruitment

10 months

IT Officer

March 2022 - Present (10 months)

Davao, Davao Region, Philippines

As IT Officer:

-Installing and configuring computer hardware, software, systems, networks, printers, and scanners

- -Monitor and maintain computer systems and networks
- -Troubleshoot system and network problems, diagnosing and solving hardware or software faults
- -Set up new users' accounts and profiles and deal with password issues
- -Administer the installation file access, user access, Wi-Fi restriction, and overall network functionality
- -Plan, organize, control, and evaluate IT and electronic data operations

CRM Officer

March 2022 - Present (10 months)

Davao, Davao Region, Philippines

As Client Relations Officer:

- -Assist in enforcing plans that will help meet the standards and needs of the clients
- -Maintains client confidence and protects operations by keeping information confidential
- -Support the Client Relationships, Training and Development department: attending and facilitating client interviews, attending client meetings if necessary, conducting briefings and technical interviews, escalating and resolving areas of concern as raised by clients, etc.

WCA Travel

Independent Affiliate

May 2022 - Present (8 months)

AubrainTours, an affiliate of WCA, provides affordable, competitive and quality travel accommodations and packages to individuals and families worldwide.

Web Portal: https://www.wcatravel.com/aubraintours/ Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aubraintours/

TAIPAN DEVELOPMENT CORPORATION

Information Technology Specialist November 2019 - February 2022 (2 years 4 months)

Region XI - Davao, Philippines

Gaisano Capital Mintal Davao

- -Maintain and administer computer networks and related computing environments including computer hardware, systems software, application sofware, and all configuration.
- -Diagnose, troubleshoot, and resolve hardware, software, or other network and system problems, replace defective components when necessary.

- -Oversee the daily performance of computer systems.
- -Answer user inquiries regarding computer software or hardware operation to resolve problems.
- -Set up equipment for employee use, performing or ensuring proper installation of cables, operating systems, or appropriate software.
- -Install and perform minor repairs to hardware, software, or peripheral equipment.

Department of Social Welfare and Development Data Encoder January 2020 - January 2020 (1 month)

DSWD Listahanan - National Household Targeting System for Poverty Reduction (NHTS - PR)

Davao City Water District Technical Support Intern April 2018 - May 2018 (2 months) Region XI - Davao, Philippines

Teleperformance
Technical Support Representative
April 2017 - July 2017 (4 months)
Region XI - Davao, Philippines

Walk through customers in cable box and modem activation via phone call.

iCan English Online Co. Ltd.
Online English Teacher
December 2015 - July 2016 (8 months)
Region XI - Davao, Philippines

Teach English language to Koreans

Education

University of Mindanao
Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering · (2013 - 2019)